Lines missing in latest version

Moodles.txt
	changed:

	new:


Sandbox.txt
	changed:

	new:
		Sandbox_ETW_PetTherapy = "Pet Therapy",
		Sandbox_ETW_PetTherapySkill = "Pet Therapy Husbandry Skill Requirement",
		Sandbox_ETW_PetTherapyUniqueAnimalsPetted = "Pet Therapy Unique Animals Petted",
		Sandbox_ETW_PetTherapyUniqueAnimalsPetted_tooltip = "How many different animals you have to pet to qualify for gaining Pet Therapy",
		Sandbox_ETW_PetTherapyMoodBoostMultiplier = "Pet Therapy Mood Boost Multiplier",
		Sandbox_ETW_PetTherapyMoodBoostMultiplier_tooltip = "Multiplier to Pet Therapy mood boost. By default, petting decreases Panic, Stress, Boredom and Unhappiness by 1%. Setting this to, for example, 4 would make it so decrease is 1% * 4 = 4%",
		Sandbox_ETW_PetTherapyMinutesBetweenPets = "Pet Therapy time between mood boost",
		Sandbox_ETW_PetTherapyMinutesBetweenPets_tooltip = "Time in minutes that players have to wait since last petting action that gave mood boost for new boost to be applied. Petting animals in this time window will not give mood boost but it will also not reset the timer, so you don't have to manually keep track when can you pet again.",

		Sandbox_ETW_BladeEnthusiast = "Blade Enthusiast",
		Sandbox_ETW_BladeEnthusiastSkill = "Blade Enthusiast Long Blade Skill requirement",
		Sandbox_ETW_BladeEnthusiastKills = "Blade Enthusiast Long Blade Kills requirement",
		
		Sandbox_ETW_PolearmFighter = "Polearm Fighter",
		Sandbox_ETW_PolearmFighterSkill = "Polearm Fighter Spear Skill requirement",
		Sandbox_ETW_PolearmFighterKills = "Polearm Fighter Spear Kills requirement",


UI.txt
	changed:
		UI_ETW_Options_GatherDetailedDebug_tooltip = "Enables prints into console.txt. Useful for debug purposes, also allows you to find data about internal counters. Ctrl+F for 'ETW' to find the loggers. Adds a lot of unneeded (for players) info into console.txt which might have performance impact the longer you play, enable this only when reporting bugs with console logs.",
		UI_ETW_Options_ReadMe_tooltip = "Please note that there are both sandbox settings and mod option settings in this mod. In 99% of the cases whatever you want to enable/disable/change can be changed. This includes sound notifications, hotkeys, this UI adjustments, and a hundred of other settings. Sandbox settings are in sandbox settings, obviously. Cleint-Side Mod Options and Hotkeys can be found in Esc -> Options -> Mods -> Evolving Traits World.",



	new:
		UI_trait_PolearmFighter = "Polearm Fighter",
		UI_trait_PolearmFighterDesc = "You've mastered the art of fighting with long, pole-like weapons. From pitchforks to spears, you know how to keep threats at bay with reach and precision",

		UI_trait_BladeEnthusiast = "Blade Enthusiast",
		UI_trait_BladeEnthusiastDesc = "A deep appreciation for edged weapons and the discipline to wield them effectively. You've honed your skills with long blades, making every strike count",
